[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This genetic disorder is characterized by the premature fusion of the bones of the skull, which affects the shape of the head and face.", "correct_answer": "Pfeiffer syndrome", "incorrect_answers": ["Angelman syndrome", "Joubert syndrome", "Klinefelter syndrome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Waynes World movie, from where is Wayne and Garths live cable-access show broadcast?", "correct_answer": "Waynes basement", "incorrect_answers": ["Waynes bedroom", "Wayne and Garths school", "Garths living room"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These words were delivered by Scottish national hero William Wallace, who was featured in what 1995 movie: Aye, fight and you may die, run, and youll live ...   at least for awhile.?", "correct_answer": "Braveheart", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bruce", "The Black Prince", "The Warrior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pornography is illegal on the Internet.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A flash of lightning can heat the air around it, which gives off vibrations and expansion of the air thus causing what?", "correct_answer": "Thunder", "incorrect_answers": ["Tornadoes", "Hail", "Finger lightning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the pineapple plant (Ananas comosus)?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It is a herbaceous plant", "It grows to 1-1.5 meters (3.3 to 4.9 ft) tall", "It is a perennial plant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is the white woman appearing at the Belchen Tunnel in Switzerland described according to the urban legend?", "correct_answer": "Old woman in white clothes", "incorrect_answers": ["Headless woman wearing a white dress", "Pregnant woman in white clothes", "African woman in white dress"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie won 3 Razzies in 2003?", "correct_answer": "Gigli", "incorrect_answers": ["Over the Top", "Rambo Part IV: The Testimony", "Glitter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the the body length of an average mature sloth from head to tail?", "correct_answer": "50-60 centimeters", "incorrect_answers": ["90-100 centimeters", "70-80 centimeters", "30-40 centimeters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the second war fought by the USA?", "correct_answer": "The War of 1812", "incorrect_answers": ["The War against the Barbary Pirates", "The Civil War", "The Mexican War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Ryan and Sharpays last name in the film High School Musical?", "correct_answer": "Evans", "incorrect_answers": ["Times", "Smith", "Johnson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these pearls are the most valuable in the world?", "correct_answer": "Natural pearls that are perfectly spherical", "incorrect_answers": ["Natural pearls with the most unusual shapes", "Cultured pearls with spherical shape", "None of these"]}]